

Tchinda Takoubo Dilane

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Software Engineer graduated from the University of the Mountains of Bangangté in Cameroon, I have developed advanced technical skills during my academic internships, and my two years as a Working Student at Tonkain, and more recently with my new full time position at MesinTech. I am currently looking for a new opportunity in the field.

CONTACT

dilanettd@gmail.com



+237 656369040



Douala, Cameroun



https://www.linkedin.com/in/dilanetchinda-takoubo-86224b161/

SOFTWARE & SKILLS

Programming languages

Java, Python, C, C++, JavaScript, jQuery, TypeScript, Sass, HTML, CSS, PHP.

Framworks

Angular, Spring, SpringBoot, Django, Flask, Bootstrap, ReactJS, ElectronJS, JavaFX, JavaEE, Laravel, Express.

Text editors & tools

VsCode, IntelliJ, Pycharm, AndroidStudios, Git, Github, npm, pip, Maven, gradle, MySQL, MongoDB, Postgres, FireBase, CMS (WordPress, Droopal), UML, Merise, PowerAMC, Agile SCRUM.

Competencies

- Mastery Full stack web development with (Angular, ReactJS, Flask ,Django ,SpringBoot, JavaEE and Laravel);
- Mastery of RESTful web services;
- Mastery Security of RESTful web services (JWT and OAuth2.0);
- Mastery Native Android mobile application development;
- Mastery of Destop development (Java, ElectronJS);
- Master of the Git version control tool;
- Moderate knowledge of the Agile SCRUM method.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer | MesinTech

2022 – 2022 Douala, Cameroun

- Front and back-end development on web projects;
- Maintenance on various project;
- Advice and implementation of projects in

Working Student | Tonkaln

2020 – 2022 Bangangté, Cameroun

- Android mobile development with Android Studios;
- Python Web Development with Flask and Django;
- Computer maintenance.

Internship | Matrix Telecoms

2019 - 2019 Yaundé, Cameroun

- Network maintenance;
- Network supervision;
- Design and implementation of a VoIP solution.

EDUCATION

MASTER IN COMPUTER AND SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

Université des montagnes | Bangangté, Cameroun 2020 - 2021

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER NETWORKS AND TELECOMMUNICATIONS

Université des montagnes | Bangangté, Cameroun 2016 - 2019

GENERAL SCIENTIFIC BACCALAUREATE

Lycée bilingue de Ndikiniméki | Ndikinimeki, Cameroun 2015 - 2016

LANGUAGES

French English

HOBBIES

Football, Jeux Vidéos, Film, Série, Mangas, Musique.